No!
You're kidding me.
My next punch will end this.
Get ready!
Ahhhh!
Huh?
Ahhhhhh! Ahhhhhh!
Wait, what happened?
When did he get heads?
Nobody hit him at all—it's a side effect
of that cannonball form of his now.
For the next 10 minutes or so, you can't
use any hockey—that's how it works!
it works All that power comes at a cost.
But it looks like a good trade-off to me.
Those punches really
did a number on Kaido.
It's our chance to finish him off!
You little oafs are pushing
your luck again, I see!
Come on, Lupi.
If you don't move, you'll die!
That was fast.
Worn out already.
Well, it was a lovely rampage.
But all good things must
come to an end, as they say.
Happy Mother's Day!
Now, hand over, saw hat, or get burnt!
Counter-shock!
Luffy, wake up!
Come on, killer, we gotta keep the
pressure on him! Let's go! Roger!
Kill her!
Brace yourself!
The wind that blows from the
heavens shall rend the land asunder!
Dragon Twister!
Kill her!
This is ridiculous.
That's our second natural
disaster in one day.
Zoro, you saved me.
Of course.
Luffy!
Hey, you big lizard!
You got another thing coming if you
think I'm gonna let you eat my captain!
Oh, my God.
There it is again, that strange Haki.
I can sense it coming from his blade.
Three-Sword Style, Black
Rope, Dragon Quister!
He cut his scales!
Oh, good look at that!
That little punk hurt Kaido!
This pain is familiar.
I see.
It seems my suspicions were correct.
How did you end up with Odin's blade?
You think your dragon
twister can stand up to mine?
You need to learn your place.
Hey, come on, Murphy.
Laura, is that you?
We've got another big one coming!
Dragon Twister!
Demolition Dust!
What a mess.
This evening has not gone as planned.
Our supplier getting
beheaded was bad enough.
But now the entire banquet
has become a battlefield.
seems to be an act of vengeance in the
name of a ruler who died 20 years ago
wano's history aside this
shouldn't come as a surprise
the moment that doflamingo
fell from power a clash
between kaido and the worst
generation became inevitable
and now we're dealing with
the perfect storm only fate
could bring the samurai and
pirates together at a time
like this soon right before
our eyes the world will
be turned on its head it's
unlikely but think of what
would happen if both emperors
were taken down at once
It would be chaos impossible to predict
But we need not worry about that
The invaders are here and
their numbers are clear
Fifty-four hundred or something near
Minus the four hundred dead, I fear
How did we fare, you say?
Beast pirates are surely winning the day.
30,000 have entered the fray,
but 3,000 are dead to our dismay.
I must say, the samurai did a fine job.
Because of their difference in numbers,
they couldn't even reach Kaido
if they attacked head-on.
Deciding to launch a surprise assault
was surely the correct choice.
It was their only choice.
But this battle won't end even
if they take Kaido's head!
This is an Alto war.
There's no refuge on the island.
Kaido's officers are absurdly powerful.
If they don't finish them off as well,
they'll butcher the
samurai 100 men at a time?
It's up to the worst
generation to defeat them.
No one else can do it.
Otherwise, this game of Go will
end with a board full of black.
It's too early to say
which side will prevail.
Do your best to kill each
other, you filthy pirates.
What the hell did he transform?
That must be his man—beast form!
I'll be damned in.
Then I gotta admit this is fun!
Took the words right
out of my mouth—you've?
mouth you've You've really
thrown quite the party!
Nooo!
KIDEL!
Listen up, everyone!
To break the deadlock, Master Queen
entrusted me with a secret weapon.
Something to leave the enemy
quaking in their boots.
Yay!
And might I say, you're looking as
majestic as ever, General Speed.
Okay, sounds great.
Where's the weapon, though?
Why, it's right here.
My skin shimmers like the sun. Flawless.
As resilient as iron.
And my muscles, they pulse with strength!
You want one?
Whoa! Incredible!
You know, that's starting
to look real good to me.
I need that dumpling now!
Fuck it over, damn you!
Seems like you've suffered
quite the loss, Briscola.
What happened?
Never mind that.
The point is, I gotta get my
revenge on the Straw Hats.
And if it takes this miracle dumpling of
yours to do that, then put it in my mouth!
Far be it from me to stop you
once you eat one of these.
Your whole world will change here.
Well, how is it?
General, hmm,
feels like it might be working
or it might not be working.
What a load of nonsense!
Don't you know this ability
enhancing dumpling is
a masterpiece made by none
other than master queen?
Surely you're not saying it's a failure?
Perhaps you'd like to tell him in person.
Yeah,
I feel it now.
Suddenly a surge of power is.
coursing through my veins!
That's awesome!
Oh, I gotta get me one, too!
General speed!
May I have a doubling too, pretty please?
And one for me!
Two for us!
No need to fear!
I have enough for all gifters!
Help yourselves!
Hooray!
Ah, oh!
Mm-hmm.
Delicious!
As soon as you finish eating,
get ready to join the battle.
We can't afford to waste time.
The Straw Hats are giving their best.
We have to do the same.
Risa-Lina, I wanna go!
I wanna go to Onigashima with everyone!
And I don't blame them
for leaving me behind.
Even if it makes me sad, so please—he,
what that frown off your face, master!
master
Keep me down!
That's enough, Master.
Please stop.
You need to rest and recover.
I'm okay.
I can't buy Kaido myself.
This is the only way I can help.
I'm okay!
I have to be okay and I have
to be brave enough to do this!
This is the future of my country too!
A future without Kaido and Odoji!
That's worth fighting for!
I mean, I can't be hungry
for the rest of my life.
I want to eat real food whenever I want.
I understand.
We're here to help you!
Yeah, don't worry!
Let's have a meal first then hide
and wait for our chance to strike
That's right, my fellow
gifters, eat them all up!
Hey, look!
I think that's Difugo,
the vice warden from Udon!
You're dead!
I'm gonna pay you back for all
the suffering you caused us!
Sorry about that, guys.
Can we call it water
under the bridge for now?
What? Watch out!
General Difugo, sir!
Pleased to see you!
Thank you, but let's cut the
formalities. Eat this! Eat this!
Eat this!
Now serve the master and serve her well!
General!
Whoa!
Boy, where that came from!
I can't believe what I just saw!
This is the end!
Hold down the robot and don't let go!
Hey, that's cheating.
I can't win with you guys on me.
Yeah, that's the idea, you big metal dope.
You may be tough, but there's no
way you can shake off all of us.
Don't underestimate us.
We're all gifters with superhuman powers.
We got you locked down, pal.
Oh, he's right.
They're strong as hell.
Uh...
Franky!
Huh?
That sounds like...
Usa! Nami!
Agotama!
Why are you here?
Actually, never mind.
I'm kind of in a pinch right now.
Can you guys help me out here?
I got all these dudes
piled up on me, and...
Huh?
Help us!
Brave me!
Geez, they got it worse than me!
They actually scratched that!
Now I'm in double trouble!
Gifters, keep doing what you're doing!
Block their escape!
Now do you see how outnumbered you are?
Even if you win here,
you'd have to turn the tide all
across the island to stand a chance!
Oh crap, I'm so screwed!
That's right!
I came here to turn the tide, and
that's exactly what I'm going to do!
Hey, you guys!
Listen up!
Go help Rondo's stake!
Son-Hack-Breeeek!
You got it, bastard!
What?
Ugh, okay then.
Tang, you nearly busted me up!
Don't touch!
I found my face again!
What do you think you're
doing, you idiots?
Sasaki!
That's one, ulti!
What the hell is going on?
Switch over to the enemy's side!
Strike the bastards down!
They did what?
But we're winning!
What do they have to gain
by siding with the samurai?
They're probably using some
stupid Devil Fruit power!
You guys are the worst!
You're begging for a headbutt,
and I've got plenty to go around!
Can't take a hint, huh?
Here's your lightning alert!
This might put you into cardiac
arrest, so good luck with that!
Thunder win!
Go! Go!
Fix this!
That sucked.
I can't move.
You're getting double the
headbutts next time, bitch!
I had a feeling that wouldn't be enough.
Looks like I need more powerful
lightning to finish the job.
You think you're pretty tricky, huh?
Take those pirates down immediately.
This could get ugly if we let them go.
Aye aye, Sasaki sir!
I got this!
Dumpling star!
What did I just swallow?
Hey, everybody!
We're friends now!
Follow me!
Aye aye, Master!
What the hell, did the whole
armor division just turn on me?
Hey, get back here, dammit!
Careful, Pa.
You're still in a fight, remember?
Better pay attention.
Or I'm gonna wreck ya.
Franken-sword!
Leave for victory!
Damn it.
What the hell did you do to me?
The fun's over; I'm not
playing games with you.
Be a good boy, black leg.
What a pity?
I wish I could have
teased you all night long.
You're powerless against us.
You took down so many men
without a hint of mercy,
but before women like us,
you won't lift a finger.
Your sad little life is
in the palm of my hand.
I could end it in an instant.
Now do as I say.
Call for Nico Robin.
Cayman lady here will help you.
All you have to do is speak loudly to her.
Then your words will be
transmitted across the castle.
Well, do that and I'll set you free.
That's a rare mercy from Kaido himself.
And what if I do?
What'll you do to her?
Let's see.
Me and my girls will
ambush her, of course.
Then maim her arms and legs
so she can never escape.
But don't worry.
The mission we need her help for
could take years to complete.
So we won't kill her.
Not right away.
Trust me, she won't make
it that easy for you.
I found them!
It's the Akazaya Samurai!
They couldn't hide from me!
Like I thought, they got away
from the rooftop, but guess what?
They're covered in blood!
And are they still alive? Yes! Barely.
They're at the back of the castle tower!
Go, go, go!
The second floor of the treasure
repository at the second Fall!
They must have escaped from Kaido.
Someone else handling.
I'm busy now.
Get to the treasure repository immediately
and finish off the Akazaya Samurai.
What is your answer, my lady?
yes king of course i'll go there
shortly the treasure repository is near
here i'll settle the matter in no
time once i finish administering some
discipline just get the job done
Kin'emon they lost wait don't go hey just
so you know there's 10 people in that
room careful it's so It's so dark,
I can't see very well,
but there's one extra
person helping the samurai.
Don't know who, but kill
them too while you're at it.
Someone's in there, but who?